# **Bri Pepper**

Phone: (217) 577-3065 | Email: <a href="mailto:bripepr@gmail.com">bripepr@gmail.com</a> | Denver, CO

LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/bri-pepper/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/bri-pepper/</a>

Portfolio: www.bpepper.design

UX/UI Designer with a background in the arts, pastry design, and healthcare. Certificate in UX/UI Design from the University of Denver with skills in User Research, Visual Prototyping & Wireframes, User Interface. Strengths in design, creative thinking, critical thinking, teamwork, designing and building projects based on the design process: Empathy, Define, Ideate, Prototype, Test.

### **Technical Skills**

User Research, User Interviewing, Persona Creation, Storyboarding, Heuristic Evaluation, User Flows, Task Flows, Journey Mapping, Value Proposition, Card Sorting, Sketching, Wireframing and Prototyping, User Interface, Style Guides, Color Theory, A/B Testing, Presenting Case Studies

# **Projects**

**Peeps For Pets |** User Experience Researcher/Designer/User Interface Designer <a href="https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1htEdjif\_JPe3IV2F5\_eaRKxtoO-TRrUE2B8rdykKS9Y/edit?usp=sharing">https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1htEdjif\_JPe3IV2F5\_eaRKxtoO-TRrUE2B8rdykKS9Y/edit?usp=sharing</a>
This project was focused on designing an app that pairs potential pet owners with potential pets based on their personality traits and lifestyles; reducing the rate in which pets are returned to shelters.

 Skills | Technologies Used: User Research (Interviews, Surveys) Analyzed Data (Sorted Notes, Miro, FigmaJam) Utilized Research Methods (Persona Creation, User Flows, Storyboarding) Prototyping & Wireframing (Figma, FigJam), User Testing/Usability Testing

A Little Help Redesign | User Experience Researcher/Designer/User Interface Designer

https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1FJiOmrxa-rTuj\_eSH-RNECVLrUiaoQVf/edit?usp=sharing&ouid=106962949468
686387652&rtpof=true&sd=true

The goal of this project was to redesign the website of "A Little Help," a volunteer website to help eldery individuals with daily tasks, so that it was accessible and functional for the User.

 Skills | Technologies Used: User Research (Interviews, Surveys), Stakeholder Interviews, Analyzed Data, Utilized Research Methods, Prototyping & Wireframing, User Testing/Usability Testing, Accessibility Testing, Figma, FigJam, Miro

**Nourish |** User Experience Researcher/Designer/User Interface Designer

<a href="https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1sKQusaxX6htT8X8N2D4hr-NcApbdUcdI7BNnN-NJctU/edit?usp=sharing">https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1sKQusaxX6htT8X8N2D4hr-NcApbdUcdI7BNnN-NJctU/edit?usp=sharing</a>

This project was centered on designing a sustainable shopping app where Users could find sustainable products on one platform from their favorite stores.

 Skills | Technologies Used: User Research (Interviews, Surveys) Analyzed Data, Utilized Research Methods, Prototyping & Wireframing, User Testing/Usability Testing, Front End Development, Figma, FigJam, Miro

# **Work Experience**

#### ZimmerBiomet | Remote/CO

August 2022 - Present

#### **Customer Service Representative**

- Demonstrated resourcefulness by finding creative solutions to complex issues, optimizing processes and improving overall efficiency
- Utilized an invoicing system to accurately process and track invoices, ensuring timely payments and maintaining financial records.
- Effectively communicated with team members and facilities to coordinate tasks, resolve issues, and ensure smooth workflow
- Demonstrated strong multitasking abilities by managing and prioritizing multiple tasks simultaneously, meeting deadlines consistently
- Successfully met end-of-day and end-of-week deadlines for various projects, ensuring timely completion and delivery
- Maintained a positive and proactive attitude, approaching challenges with a can-do mindset and a willingness to learn and adapt

## Cosmo's Dog Bakery & Pet Supplies | Wheat Ridge, CO

July 2021 - August 2022

#### **Customer Service Associate**

- Assists customers, conduct research on products + nutrition
- Correcting inventory in Square POS to have an accurate count of products to help the manager with ordering products and see what products are selling well or not selling well
- Helping to increase the number of new customers a day from 1 new customer a day to an average of 5+
  new customers a day with friendly service and encouragement to shop for quality products
   increasing
  sales almost 3 times what it was in the past year

# The Yum Factory | Quincy, IL

April 2018 - March 2019

#### Cake Designer/Bakery Manager

- Planned out orders for the week, assigned each project a timeline during the week to be completed to
  ensure orders were always ready by deadline
- Designed orders based on customer wants/needs resulting in unique products that made the business competitive and gain attention from new customers
- Became a highly requested designer for pastries and praised for ability to make custom designs as close as possible to customers ideas/images
- Communicated efficiently with Owner and other employees so that there was a smooth process for both employees/customers

#### Education

Certificate, UX/UI January 2022

University of Denver

Associate of Arts May 2015

John Wood Community College